[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "What does CSS stand for ?",
"a": "Computer Style Sheets",
"b": "Colorful Style sheets",
"c": "Casecading Style Sheets",
"d": "Creative Style System",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "CSS file extension ?",
"a": ".html",
"b": ".js",
"c": ".css",
"d": ".style",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "Selects all elements in CSS ?",
"a": ".",
"b": "#",
"c": "*",
"d": "all",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "CSS is used for ?",
"a": "Adding animations",
"b": "Styling wed pages",
"c": "Writing logic",
"d": "Writing logic",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "CSS border style ?",
"a": "border-type",
"b": "style-border",
"c": "border-style",
"d": "border-line",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "To make corners round ?",
"a": "corner-size",
"b": "border-round",
"c": "curve-corner",
"d": "border-radius",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "Change font type ?",
"a": "font-type",
"b": "font-family",
"c": "text-font",
"d": "font-style",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": " CSS stands for ?",
"a": "Cascading Style Sheets",
"b": "Creating Style System",
"c": "Computer Style Sheets",
"d": "Color Style Sheets",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "Preperty to control width",
"a": "element-width",
"b": "box-width",
"c": "size",
"d": "width",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "What does <ul> stand for ?",
"a": "Upper list",
"b": "Underrlined List",
"c": "User list",
"d": "Unordered list",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
}
]